Vivien Kellems Papers 1992.0033
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Personal Papers, undated, 1883-1975
  - A - C, 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 362)
  - Boby Baker-Estes, 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 363)
  - Connecticut, 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 364-365)
  - New York, 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 366-267)
  - S - Texas, 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 368)
  - V - W, 1964, 1968 (Box 16:, Folder 369)
  - A, 1965-1966 (Box 17:, Folder 370)
  - California - Washington D.C., 1965 (Box 17:, Folder 371)
  - Colorado - Washington D.C., 1965-1966 (Box 17:, Folder 372)
  - Connecticut, 1965 (Box 17:, Folder 373-376)
  - California, 1966 (Box 17:, Folder 377-378)
  - Connecticut, 1966 (Box 17:, Folder 379-382)
  - Foreign, Massachusetts and Vermont, 1966 (Box 17:, Folder 383)
  - Glass, 1966 (Box 17:, Folder 384)
  - New York, North Carolina and Texas, 1966 (Box 17:, Folder 385)
  - A, 1967-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 386)
  - California - Colorado, 1967-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 387)
  - Connecticut, 1967-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 388-391)
  - Florida - Foreign, 1967-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 392)
  - Georgia - Mississippi, 1967-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 393)
  - Glass, 1967-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 394)
  - Kansas - L, 1967-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 395)
  - M - N, 1967 (Box 18:, Folder 396)
  - New Jersey and New York, 1967-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 397)
  - Organic Gardening Newsletters, 1967-1968, 1971-1972 (Box 18:, Folder 398)
  - O - W, 1967-1968 (Box 18:, Folder 399)
  - Alabama - Colorado, 1969 (Box 18:, Folder 400)
  - Connecticut, 1969 (Box 18:, Folder 401-402)
  - Florida, Foreign, Indiana, Illinois, 1969 (Box 18:, Folder 403)
  - L - M, 1969 (Box 18:, Folder 404)
  - New York City, 1969 (Box 18:, Folder 405)
  - N - O, 1969 (Box 18:, Folder 406)
  - Rhode Island - Wyoming, 1969 (Box 18:, Folder 407)
  - A, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 408)
  - California, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 409-410)
  - Connecticut, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 411-413)
  - Colorado - Indiana, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 414)
  - Foreign, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 415)
  - Kansas - M, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 416)
  - N, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 417)
  - O, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 418)
  - P - Washington, 1970-1971 (Box 19:, Folder 419)
  - W, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 420)
  - Washington - Wyoming, 1970-1971 (Box 19:, Folder 421)
  - A, 1971 (Box 19:, Folder 422)
  - Anonymous Letters, 1971-1972 (Box 19:, Folder 423)
  - California, 1971 (Box 19:, Folder 424)
  - Connecticut, 1971 (Box 20:, Folder 425-428)
  - Colorado, 1971 (Box 20:, Folder 429)
  - Washington D.C., 1971 (Box 20:, Folder 430)
  - Florida - Foreign, 1971 (Box 20:, Folder 431)
  - Illinois - Kansas, 1971 (Box 20:, Folder 432)
  - Massachusetts, 1971 (Box 20:, Folder 433)
  - Minnesota - New Jersey, 1971 (Box 20:, Folder 434)
  - New York, 1971 (Box 20:, Folder 435-440)
  - O - R, 1971 (Box 20:, Folder 441)
  - A, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 442)
  - California, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 443)
  - Colorado - Delaware, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 444)
  - Connecticut, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 445-449)
  - Washington D.C., 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 450)
  - Florida - M, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 451)
  - Foreign, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 452)
  - N - Oregon, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 453)
  - Pennsylvania - Wisconsin, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 454)
  - Reader's Digest, 1972-1973 (Box 21:, Folder 455)
  - Washington, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 456)
  - Alabama - Colorado, 1973 (Box 21:, Folder 457-458)
  - Bob Packwood, U.S. Senate, 1973 (Box 21:, Folder 459)
  - Connecticut, 1973 (Box 21:, Folder 460-461)
  - Washington D.C. - Massachusetts, 1973 (Box 22:, Folder 462)
  - Foreign, 1973 (Box 22:, Folder 463)
  - Michigan - Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 22:, Folder 464)
  - Texas - Wisconsin, 1973 (Box 22:, Folder 465)
  - Alabama - Washington D.C., 1974 (Box 22:, Folder 466)
  - Connecticut, 1974 (Box 22:, Folder 467)
  - Florida - New York, 1974 (Box 22:, Folder 468)
  - Ohio - Wisconsin, 1974 (Box 22:, Folder 469)
  - Connecticut, 1975 (Box 22:, Folder 470)
  - Documents after Death, 1975-1976 (Box 22:, Folder 471)
  - Oversize documents, 1957-1969 (Box OS:, Folder 472)
  - Photographs, 1938-1974 (Box 23:, Folder 473-474)
  - Photographs, negatives, epehmera and memorabilia, undated (Box 27)
  - Photographs, audio cassettes and tape, color slides, certificates, ephemera and memorabilia, undated (Box 49)
  - Photographs (B&W prints), undated (Box 50)
  - Scrapbooks (photographs, clippings, flyers), 1928-1942 (Box 51)
  - Scrapbook (photographs, clippings, flyers), 1943 (Box 53)
  - Subseries A: Sorted Correspondence, undated, 1933-1950
    - (Folder 54)
      - Aetna Life Insurance, 1936
      - Allard, Leola, 1937
      - Atherton, Gertrude, 1936
      - Bagueley, Noel ("Softie"), 1937
      - Baird, Edgar ("Ted"), 1942
      - Baker, Bryant, 1936
      - Baldwin, Evangeline, 1941
      - Beach, Dorothy, 1941
      - Benjamin, Harry, 1936
      - Benson, John B., 1936
      - Billington, Donna Jean, 1936
      - Bolster, Maude and Frank, 1936
      - Bonaire, L., 1936
      - Brookfield, Frank, 1936
      - California Earthworm Farms, 1942
      - Callanan, E. E., 1937
      - Carlson, Roy, 1939
      - Citrano, Christine, 1942
      - Clarke Electric Co., 1936
      - Clarke, Adela, 1940
      - Clarke, Florence, 1940
      - Cleaver, Ralph ("Rafe"), 1936
      - Clucao, Joe, 1942
      - Coleman, O. K., 1937
      - Coley, Pearl, 1937
      - Collens, Clarence ("Buddy"), 1936
      - Collens, Charles ("Carl"), 1937
      - Collins, Ashton, 1936
      - Coni and Covington ( England), 1940-1943
      - Conley, Edward James, 1940
      - Connecticut Light & Power, 1936
      - Connor, Michael A. (CTDMV), 1936
      - Coonan, J. E., 1937
      - Coto, Julio C., 1937
      - D'Almeida, Armando, 1938
      - de Silva, Jorge, 1938
      - Dillon, Mary E., 1940
      - Dotty, 1936
      - Dunbar, Virginia and Jack, 1941
      - Dunn, Frank, 1937
      - Fairey, E., undated
      - Fidelity Title & Trust Co., 1940
      - First National Bank of Eugene, Oregon, 1940
      - Flynn, Blanche, 1938
      - Foley, Peter, 1937
      - Forbes, Helen, 1937
      - Gates, Dottie, undated
      - Gavin, Basil, 1939
      - Gilmore, Samuel, 1938
      - Goble, Lena, 1940
      - Grossman, George, 1937
      - Hamilton, 1937
      - Hampton, J. W., 1939
      - Hansen, 1939
      - Harris, Sara ("Sue"), 1937
      - Haskins, Ethel, 1941
      - Hawkins, Emmie, 1938
      - Hofe, George Douglas, 1940
      - Holmes, Jewel and Dwight, 1937
      - Hsu, Jabin, 1933
      - Jacobs, Whipple, 1941
      - Jamison, Hugh, 1939
      - Jammer, J., 1938
      - Kiener, David, 1937
      - Kobak, Edgar, 1937
      - Kodym, Harold, undated
      - Kroner, Alberto, 1940
      - Longman, Walter, 1936
      - Low, Elsa, 1938
      - Luman, Dottie, 1936
      - Harji, Malik, 1940
      - Mann, Conklin ("Kink"), 1936
      - Mansfield, K. W., 1940
      - Mason, Veyne, 1938
      - Matthews, Claude, 1934-1936
      - McMullin, Loretta, 1936
      - Miller, T. Lee, 1937
      - Montanaro, Vincent, 1940
      - Morio, 1936
      - Nafe, Ann, 1938
      - Nehls, Herbert, 1939
      - Northwest Christian College (mother attended), 1941
      - Peck, A. J., 1936
      - Pengra, Charles, 1936
      - Pinto, Fernando, undated
      - Pollock, Channing, 1937
      - Pollock, John C., 1940
      - Pullman Co., 1937
      - Pullman & Comley, 1936
      - Randall, Jesse, undated
      - Reardon, Ebba, undated
      - Reed, Joseph Verner, undated
      - Reed, May, undated
      - Riegger, Adolph L., undated
      - Roberts, Jane L., 1941
      - Rolfs, Maria, 1936
      - Schwartz, Anne, 1939
      - Schwartz & Bluestein, 1941
      - Singh, J. J., 1936
      - Snow, John Howland, undated
      - Stoddard, Milton A., 1941
      - Thompson-Taylor, Wullie, 1937
      - Thune, Erik, 1938
      - Tynan, Olive, 1950
      - Verhulsen, 1939
      - Wake, Hereward, 1940
      - Watson, Stewart, 1938
      - Watson, Stewart, 1940
      - Wilbraham, R. H., 1936
      - Willkie, Wendell L., 1941
      - Williams, George B., 1937
      - Widmer's Wine Cellars, 1937
      - Wood, George W. ("Ollie"), 1936
      - W. B. Wooley & Co., Ltd. ( England), 1940
        General note
        [letters include descriptions of bombing in London]
      - United Engineers & Constructors, Inc., 1936
      - Conlon Corp. (Washers and dryers), 1939
      - Zavattaro, Mario, 1940
      - Zedlitz, Frederic von, 1938-1946
- Series III: Activism Papers, undated, 1879-1975
  - (Box 29)
    - Political newsletters, 1948-1949
    - Political leaflets and booklets, 1943-1944
    - Human events
      - 1948
      - 1949
      - 1950
      - 1972
    - Notes for speeches, undated
    - Speeches and notes, undated
    - Speech notes, 1952
    - "The House on the Beach" speech, undated
    - Articles and editorials, Public utilities, 1937
    - Publicity lists, 1958
    - Political lists, Connecticut, 1961-1962
    - American Embassy, Joseph V. Reed, 1958
    - Young Democratic Club of New Haven speech, 1958 January 29
    - Society for Advancement of Management speech, Bridgeport, CT, 1958 February 4
    - Completed speeches, Connecticut, undated
    - Medical Association Auxillary speech, New Britain, CT, 1958 May 22
    - Voting machine, 1959
    - Goodspeed Opera House, Hadlyme, CT, 1959
    - Correspondence: State officials, 1959
    - Correspondence: Finished speeches--Theatres, 1923-1925
    - Lectures resulting from Publicity, 1923-1926
    - Theatre: Speech, publicityt and contracts, undated, 1924-1925
    - Court transcript: Vivien Kellems et. al. v. United States of America et. al., 1951
    - Transcript: Premier Photo v. Director, IRS, 1964
    - Book Research--Prologue, 1967
    - Book Research--Agriculture, 1967
    - IRS exhibition, 1969
    - U.S. Tax Court: Parkside, Inc. v. Beacon Crest, Inc. v. Commissioner, Internal Revenue SErvice, 1973
    - Book Research--Epilogue, undated
    - Book Research-- California/Organic Ville, undated, 1906, 1966-1968
    - Book Research--Chaos, 1966-1967
    - Book Research--Cartoons, 1967
    - Book Research--Cities, 1965-1968
    - Book Research-- Connecticut, 1961, 1967
    - Book Research--Corruption, 1967
    - Book Research-- Dan Smoot, 1956, 1966-1967
    - Book Research--Education, undated, 1966-1967
    - Book Research--Foreign Aid, undated
    - Book Research-- Citizens Foreign Aid Committee, 1967
    - Book Research--Original, unmdated, 1907
    - Book Research--Housing, 1967
    - Book Research-- India, 1967
    - Book Research--Liberty Amendment, 1967
    - Book Research--Medical, 1967
    - Book Research--Personal publicity, 1965, 1967
    - Book Research--Poverty, 1967
    - Book Research--Privacy, 1967-1968
    - Book Research--Racial, 1967
    - Book Research--Religion, 1966-1967
    - Book Research--Tax Research, 1967
    - Book Research--Social Security, 1967
    - Book Research--Solution, undated
    - Book Research--States, 1967
    - Book Research--Taxation, 1956, 1967
    - Book Research--Treason, 1956, 1967
    - Book Research--Welfare, undated
    - Book Research--New Haven, 1879, 1967
    - Book Research--Pins, undated
    - Book Research--Furs, undated
  - (Box 30)
    - Book Research--President's wives, 1951, 1953
    - Book Research--Jokes, undated
    - Book Research--Poetry, 1951-1955
    - Book Research--Election, Connecticut, 1956
    - Book Research--Flood, Connecticut taxes, 1952-1953
    - Book Research-- Connecticut taxes, 1954-1956
    - Book Research--Baldness, 1953
    - Book Research--Age, 1953
    - Book Research--Foerign wives, 1955
    - Book Research--Working women/Housewives, 1952-1956
    - Book Research--Campaign, 1966
    - Town Meeting, 1951
    - "Toil, Taxes and Trouble,", 1951
    - Speeches, 1951
    - Information for Golden Jackass, 1946
    - Golden Jackass (11 folders), 1950
    - Vivien Kellems v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue Service, undated, 1974
    - Invitations to speak and regrets, 1941-1943
    - Political fan mail-- Connecticut, 1942
    - Publicity--A-Z, 1942-1943
    - Fan mail, Speeches and Publicity, 1942-1943
    - Blue Star mothers, 1943
    - Correspondence: Blue Star women, 1943
    - Speeches: Arkansas - Minnesota, 1943-1944
  - (Box 31)
    - Tax Speech literature and fan mail, 1943-1944
    - Speeches: Mississippi - Philadelphia, 1943-1944
    - Correspondence: Fan mail, 1944
    - Correspondence: Fan mail, 1944
    - Equal Rights Amendment Survey, 1944
    - Speeches: New York City - Wisconsin, 1944
    - Speeches: A - New York State, 1944
    - Publicity, 1944-1945
    - Speeches: notes and drafts, undated, 1945-1950
    - Correspondence: Congressional, 1945-1947
    - Speeches: fan mail, 1946
    - Correspondence: Herbert W. Clark, 1946-1947
    - Correspondence: general, 1946-1947
    - Publicity, 1946-1947
    - Curfew law: Clippings and correspondence, 1947
    - Labor issues, 1947
    - Correspondence: fan mail, 1948
    - Speeches (finished), 1948
  - (Box 32)
    - Correspondence: "Meet the Pres" program, 1948
    - Publicity, 1948
    - Correspondence: Congressional, 1948-1949
    - Speeches (finished), 1949
    - Offers of help on Witholding tax, 1948-1951
    - "Ten Demandments of Economic Order,", 1948-1951
    - Invitations to speak (3 folders), 1950
    - Invitations to speak: Alabama - Connecticut, 1951-1953
    - Invitations to speak: Delaware - Maryland, 1951-1953
    - Invitations to speak: Massachusetts - New Jersey, 1951-1953
    - Independent candidacy: Alabama - Wyoming (3 folders), 1950
    - Speeches (finished), undated, 1950-1951
    - Coalition Party ( National Association of Manufacturers), 1951
    - Contribution letters and petitions (3 folders), 1952
    - Speeches: Political campaign, 1952
    - "Power of Women," T.V. show, 1952
    - Correspondence: North Carolina - Wyoming, 1952-1953
    - Correspondence: Campaign, 1952
    - Correspondence: Alabama - Colorado, 1952-1953
    - Correspondence: Connecticut - Maryland, 1952-1953
    - Correspondence: Massachusetts - New Jersey, 1952-1953
    - Correspondence: New York, 1952-1953
  - (Box 33)
    - "Toil, Taxes, and Trouble": Books mailed and correspondence (2 folders), 1952-1953
    - Invitations to speak: New York, 1952
    - Invitations to speak: Oklahoma - Wyoming, 1952
    - Correspondence: fan mail Alabama - Connecticut, 1948-1950
    - Correspondence: fan mail Delaware - Louisiana, 1948-1950
    - Correspondence: fan mail Maine - New Jersey, 1948-1950
    - Correspondence: fan mail New York, 1948-1950
    - Correspondence: fan mail North Carolina - Wisconsin, 1948-1950
    - Publicity, 1949
    - Court records: Tax witholding, 1948-1950
    - Correspondence: Tax suit Arizona - New Jersey, 1951
    - Correspondence: Tax suit New York - West Virginia, 1951
    - Speeches (finished), 1951
    - Publicity, 1951
  - (Box 34)
    - Liberty Belles, Inc., 1952
      - Financial records (2 folders)
      - Correspondence
    - Correspondence: lawsuit with Treasury, 1967-1970
    - Rough draft of mss (3 folders), undated
    - Carbons of mss, undated
    - Lawsuit: Hartford - Middletown, 1969-1970
    - Chapter 4, undated
    - "Cows, Monkeys and Locust,", undated
    - Equal Rights Amendment, undated, 1973
    - History of the Internal Revenue Service, undated
    - Land, undated
    - History of the Internal Revenue Service after the Civil War, undated
    - Income tax after Spanish American War to 1894, undated
    - Health and Food, 1973
    - 14th Amendment, undated
    - Land grab, 1963
    - California, 1972-1973
    - Passport and money, 1968-1971
    - Correspondence: James Cornford, 1973-1974
    - Notes: "Hello Suckers,", 1968-1974
    - Chapter 2, undated
    - Chapter 3, undated
    - Chapter 1, undated
    - 4th and 5th Amendment, history of income tax, undated
    - Tax court, 1972-1974
    - Congressional Record House, 1947-1948
    - Christmas Tax Bill, 1972-1974
    - Spanish American War: notes, undated
    - Estate, Gift taxes, 1973-1974
    - Chapter 1, part 2, The Veto, undated
    - Congressional Record Senate, 1962-1972
    - Chronology of taxation, undated
    - Chapter 3, Revenue law, 1948 and implementation, undated
    - Head of household, undated
    - Waste of money, undated
    - Congressional Record, 1944
    - Congressional Record Senate, 1947-1948
    - Civil War: notes, undated
    - Book expenses, 1974
    - "You've come a long way Baby. But not quite far enough,", undated
  - (Box 35)
    - Notes: John Hanson, undated
    - Clippings: Manuscript-TV, 1972
    - Eminent Domain: HUD, 1970
    - Clippings: Thesis, undated, 1972
    - Thesis: paid bills, 1973
    - Amish, undated, 1963
    - Correspondence: Book, 1973-1974
    - Photocopies, undated
    - Mss (untitled), 1973
    - Stocks, 1971
    - Speeches (by locale), 1930-1937
    - Speeches (by locale), 1936-1937
    - Publicity, 1937
    - Publicity (2 folders), 1937-1940
    - Speeches, 1938-1942
    - Speeches: Connecticut - Massachusetts, 1939-1941
    - Speeches: Michigan - New Jersey, 1939-1941
    - Speeches: New Jersey - Ohio, 1939-1941
    - Speeches: Pennsylvania - Wisconsin, 1939-1941
    - Speeches, 1942
    - Speeches: Philadelphia - Texas, 1943-1944
    - Correspondence: California - Illinois, 1942
    - Correspondence: Kansas - Wisconsin, 1942
    - National Women's Party, 1941-1945
    - Correspondence: Betty R. Smythe, 1937-1941
    - Correspondence: Campaign, 1940-1941
    - Speeches: Special Women's Clubs, 1939
    - Speeches: Pending and deferred, 1941
    - Speeches, 1941
    - Notes: Constitution Party, 1952
    - Minute Women, undated, 1952
    - Correspondence: E. P. Dutton & Co, Inc., undated
    - Liberty Belles, Inc., 1952
    - "Power of Women" publicity plan, 1952
    - Tax Rebels, undated, 1952
    - Television code and Liberty Belles, Inc. TV contract, 1952
    - "Power of Women: scripts with flexi discs, 1952
    - Photographs: "Power of women,", 1952
    - Press releases: Senate campaign, 1952
    - Ephemera: Senate campaign, 1952
    - Flinn case, 1951
    - Campaign expenses, 1952
    - Press contacts and photographs, undated
  - (Box 36)
    - Research material: Vivien Kellems v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, undated, 1974
    - Campaign: Independence Party (3 folders), 1950
    - Correspondence: Fan mail (2 folders), 1950-1951
    - Premier Photo Service, Inc. v. Director, I.R.S. (2 folders), 1964
    - Tax court research, 1973-1974
    - Court proceedings: Election of 1956, 1958
    - Tax matter, undated, 1949-1951
    - Research, 1950
    - Correspondence: Tax (unsorted), 1950-1951
    - Correspondence and publications: unsorted, 1952-1974
    - Clippings and articles: Tax case (2 folders), undated, 1948, 1972-1974
  - (Box 37)
    - Clippings, undated
    - Notes and correspondence, 1952-1972
    - "Power of women" scripts, 1952
    - Exchange lists, undated
    - Marshall housewives, 1952
    - Liberty Belles, Inc. minutebook, 1952
    - Correspondence: Senate campaign, 1952
    - Campaign: Reports and expenses, 1952
    - Marshall housewives, 1952-1953
    - Liberty Belles, Inc. membership, 1953
    - Commissioner William J. Tracy Inspection trip, 1953
    - Women's International Exposition, 1953
    - Publication proofs, undated
    - Liberty Belles, Inc.: California, 1953
    - Labor, undated, 1948
    - Application for tax exempt status, 1953-1954
    - Gubernatorial campaign (2 folders), 1954
    - Speeches: invitations and correspondence, 1954
    - Gubernatorial campaign: Speeches and flexi discs, 1954
    - State of the Nation, 1955
    - Correspondence: Political, 1953-1955
    - "The Golden Jacka$$,", undated
    - Manuscript: "Toil, taxes and trouble,", undated
    - Resources and references, undated
  - (Box 38)
    - Radio broadcasts and speeches, undated
    - Correspondence, 1956
    - Commissioner William J. Tracy Inspection trip, 1955
    - Campaign, 1956
    - Politics (2 folders), 1956
    - Corresopndence: campaign, 1956
    - Campaign (2 folders), 1956
    - Petition case (2 folders), 1956
    - Materials ordered and speeches, 1956
    - Speeches and speech schedules, undated
    - Station WNHC-TV, New Haven, Connecticut, undated
    - Television: politics, 1956
    - Mildred Allen, Secretary of State, 1956-1957
    - Correspondence: fan mail (3 folders), 1956
  - (Box 39)
    - Correspondence: fan mail, 1956
    - Senate campaign, 1958
    - Delegates, Republican State Convention, 1956
    - Petitions, 1958
    - Mildred Allen, Secretary of State, 1958
    - Toil, taxes and troubl
      - Sales report, undated
      - Correspondence, 1958
      - Correspondence, 1959
    - Political, 1958
    - Goodspeed Opera House (4 folders), 1960
    - Rotary Club, 1961
    - Election release, undated
    - California: Trips and Speeches, undated
    - Election, 1962
    - Correspondence: Witholding tax, undated
    - Correspondence: fan mail, 1962
    - Trips and speeches, 1962
    - Invitations to speak (other than Connecticut), 1962
    - Speeches: Connecticut, 1962
    - Goodspeed Opera House, 1962
    - Correspondence: Independent Citizens Research FOundation, 1963-1964
    - Republican Citizens Cmmittee, 1963
    - Republican State Headquarters, 1964
    - Speeches: requests, 1963
    - Correspondence: fan mail, 1963-1964
    - Income Tax return, 1964
  - (Box 40)
    - Speeches, 1964
    - Speeches: REquests, 1964
    - Campaign, 1964
      - S - T
      - W
      - Hartford
      - East and West Hartford
      - I - K
      - L - M
      - N
      - O - R
      - U - V
      - Idaho
      - Illinois
      - Georgia
      - Massachusetts
      - New Jersey
      - New York
      - Texas
      - A - B
      - C - D
      - E - F
      - G - H
      - Bills and contribution lists
      - No name, no address
      - John M. Lupton
      - Correspondence: Against
      - Correspondence: TV campaign
      - California
      - Arkansas
      - Washington, D.C.
    - Hall of Free Enterprise: Arnold Bayley, 1964
    - Connecticut Republican Committee dinner, 1964
    - Speeches, 1965
    - Income tax deductions, 1965
    - Connecticut Income tax, 1965-1966
    - Income tax, 1965
    - Campaign: Photographs and clippings, 1964
    - Right to work, 1965
    - Correspondence: fan mail (2 folders), 1965
    - Republican Citizens Committee, 1965
    - Party lever, 1965
    - Correspondence: Florida, 1966
    - Correspondence: Florida, 1965
    - Correspondence: Illinois, 1965
    - Correspondence: Illinois, 1966
    - Correspondence: Iowa, 1965
    - Correspondence: Kansas, 1966
    - Correspondence: Massachusetts, 1965
    - Correspondence: Michigan, 1965
    - Correspondence: Missouri, 1965
    - Correspondence: Mississippi, 1966
    - Correspondence: Nevada, 1966
    - Correspondence: New Hampshire, 1965
    - Correspondence: New Jersy, 1965
    - Correspondence: New Jersey, 1966
    - Correspondence: New York City, 1965
    - Correspondence: Chemical Bank, 1965
    - Correspondence: New York, 1965
    - Correspondence: Oregoni, 1965
    - Correspondence: Pennsylvania, 1965
    - Correspondence: Rhode Island, 1965
    - Correspondence: Vermont, 1965
    - Correspondence: Virginia, 1965
    - Correspondence: Washington, 1965
    - Correspondence: Wisconsin, 1965
    - Correspondence: Canada, 1965
    - Income tax, 1966
    - Campaign, 1966
    - Department of Agriculture, 1966
    - Connecticut Newspapers and Television, 1966
    - Newspaper clippings, 1966
    - Correspondence: fan mail, 1966
    - Correspondence: fan mail, 1967
    - Tax, 1968
    - Press, 1969
    - Radio and television, 1969
    - Speeches, 1970
    - Press, 1970
    - Television and Radio, 1970
    - Tax, 1969
    - Tax, 1970
    - Lawsuit: New Haven data, 1969-1971
    - Lawsuit: Washington, 1970
    - Philip Long, 1970
    - Connecticut delegation: House (2 folders), 1971
    - Senate, 1971
    - D.C., 1971
    - Human Events, 1971